Lust is a many splendored thing, or is it?
How to overcome lust.
This is Doctor Paul, author of Boomer Girls: A Boomer Woman's Guide to Men and Dating and host of Ask Doctor Paul.
Lust by definition is connected with empty sex.
If you choose to be a lustful person or whatever thing you lust for, not necessarily sex but maybe it's for a hot car, maybe it's for lusting for a career, lusting for a clothing, there are many ways of defining lust, but let's look at this focus on lusting sexually.
How to overcome lust.
First you must define what you're term lust is.
Lust may be a very temporary thing.
It may be a permanent thing but typically it's a temporary thing.
It's not a longterm situation, normally it's a short term satisfied item that really is not going to affect your life.
And I would say that if it begins to affect your life, then you may want to put the controls on it, and the way you control it is to satisfy the desire with someone who is meaningful.